Register to The Harold Rome Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Scripts and Lyrics, 1934-1984; Series II; 8.3' (20 boxes)
  - Nantucket
    - Nantucket, 60, 44 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 64, Folder 79)
    - Nantucket, [17] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 64, Folder 79)
      Additional lyrics laid in
  - On Borrowed Time
    - 1963 Jan.-May, [24] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 64, Folder 80)
    - 1963 Jan.-Jun, [83] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 64, Folder 81)
      Note on discarded envelope: Early script On Borrowed Time 1963
    - On Borrowed Time, 50, 60 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 64, Folder 82)
  - Operation Spring
    Book by Arnold Auerbach
    - Operation Spring, 32, 51 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 65, Folder 83)
    - Operation Spring, 48 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 65, Folder 83)
      On title page: An untitled Musical Comedy (Act One only)
  - Pins and Needles
    Sketches by Charles Friedman and others
    - Pins and Needles, 5, 16, 10, 12 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 65, Folder 84)
      Sketches by Joseph Shrank: The harmony boys. Cream of mush. A matter of principle. What this party needs
  - Saints and Sinners
    Adapted from Paul Vincent Carroll's "Saints and Sinners"
    By Joseph Fields and Jerome Chodorov
    Music by Frederick Loewe
    - Saints and Sinners, 53, 34 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 65, Folder 85)
      Title from cover
      On title page: "A Dancin' Day" (Tentative title)
  - Sing Out the News
    Sketches by George S. Kaufman and Moss Hart
    - Sing Out the News, 61 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 65, Folder 86)
      On cover: 1st version
    - Sing Out the News, 5 parts; 28 cm. (Box 65, Folder 86)
      Typescript with additions in ink and pencil
      Five folders with lyrics labeled: Fiorello. Private enterprise. I married a Republican. Cowboy. Minstrels.
  - Sing Song Man
    By Harold Rome
    - 1949 Oct. 15, [19] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 65, Folder 86)
  - Southpaw
    Book by Ring Lardner, Jr.
    Based on the novels The Southpaw and Bang the Drum Slowly Slowly by Mark Harris
    - 1964-1969, [118] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 65, Folder 87)
      Holograph in pencil and typescript
      Note on discarded envelope: redraft and Jan. 1969 with changed pages; lyric book and work sheets
    - 1968 Jan, 36 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 65, Folder 88)
      Sheets with pencil notes
    - 1967 Apr. 14, [18] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 65, Folder 89)
    - Southpaw, [56] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 65, Folder 90)
      Note on cover: Act I (1st version)
    - Southpaw, 60, 35 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 65, Folder 91-93)
      Three copies, signed by Rome, one with additional sheets laid in
    - Southpaw, [73] sheets; 28-32 cm. (Box 66, Folder 94)
    - Southpaw, 53, 34 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 66, Folder 95)
    - Southpaw, [83] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 66, Folder 96-97)
      Two copies, one signed by Rome
    - Southpaw, 70, [16] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 66, Folder 98)
    - Southpaw, 1-19, [26], 20-65 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 66, Folder 99)
  - [Such Stuff?]
    - 1962 Aug. 1, 14 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 66, Folder 100)
      Lyrics ([22] sheets; 32 cm.)
      Holographs in pencil laid in
      Originally with the work sheets for "On Borrowed Time"
  - That's the Ticket
    Book by Julius J. and Philip G. Epstein
    - That's the Ticket, [31] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 66, Folder 101)
      Note on discarded folder: Master set of lyrics
  - Toujours Forever
    By Don Ettinger
    - 1966 Dec. 4, 68, 47 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 66, Folder 102)
    - 1967 May-Jul, [236] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 66, Folder 103)
      Act I
    - 1967 Aug. 28, [49] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 66, Folder 104)
    - Toujours Forever, 68 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 67, Folder 105)
    - Toujours Forever, 55, [37] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 67, Folder 106)
      Typescript signed by Rome
      Note on discarded folder: Toujours 1st draft
      Script labeled "Pink"
    - Toujours Forever, [61] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 67, Folder 107)
      Note: 1st draft of Act I
    - Toujours Forever, 72, 40 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 67, Folder 108)
  - Waltz of Love
    Based upon Jean Anouilh's "Waltz of the Toreadors"
    Translation by Lucienne Hill
    Book by Ed Anhalt / Ted Allan?
    Book, music, and lyrics by Harold Rome?
    - 1974 Nov. 1, 57, 28 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 67, Folder 109)
      Note on title page: 1st draft
    - 1978-1979, [119] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 67, Folder 110)
      Typescript (in part, copies)
    - Waltz of Love, [25] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 67, Folder 111)
      Typescript with ink and pencil additions
      Note on discarded folder: Waltz Toreadors - Lyrics - First draft (discarded)
    - Waltz of Love, 49, 19 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 67, Folder 112)
      Laid in: "Waltz Preliminary outline"; and memo from Anhalt to Rome and Lee Guber, 1979 Mar. 7, with sheets labeled "Structural changes" laid in
    - Waltz of Love, [66] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 67, Folder 113)
    - Waltz of Love, [85] sheets; 28-32 cm. (Box 68, Folder 114)
      Holograph in pencil and typescript with pencil and ink additions
      Note on discarded envelope: You're Mine First Draft and "Mine" crossed out and "Waltz" written in
    - Waltz of Love, 46 sheets, bound; 29 cm. (Box 68, Folder 115)
    - Waltz of Love, 57, 28 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 68, Folder 116)
      Typescript (in part, copy) with pencil additions
  - Wee Bit O' Scotch
    Book by Jerome Chodorov
    Based on a farce by W. S. Gilbert
    - Wee Bit O' Scotch, 46, 26 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 68, Folder 117)
  - Wish You Were Here
    Play by Arthur Kober and Joshua Logan
    Based upon Kober's play "Having a Wonderful Time"
    - 1950-1951, 63, 47 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 68, Folder 118)
      Note on discarded envelope: Having Wonderful (First Script of Wish You Were Here) 1950-51
    - Wish You Were Here, 82, 10, 57, A-B sheets; 28 cm. (Box 69, Folder 119)
    - Wish You Were Here, 64, 33 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 69, Folder 120)
      Steve Brown's adaptation
  - Wonder of the World
    Book by Paul Osborn from his play "On Borrowed Time"
    - Wonder of the World, 56, 57 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 69, Folder 121)
  - Wonderful Door
    Book by Howard Fast
    - 1966 Mar. 21-28, 76 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 69, Folder 122)
      Additional lyrics (holograph and typescript) laid in
      Title on title page: Tony and the Wonderful Door
  - Wonderful Things
    - Wonderful Things, 56, 57 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 69, Folder 123-124)
      Typescript (copy) with ink and pencil additions
  - Zulu and the Zayda
    By Howard Da Silva and Felix Leon
    Based on the short story by Dan Jacobson
    N.Y.: Dramatists Play Service, Inc.
    c1964
    - Zulu and the Zayda, 64 p.; 20 cm. (Box 69, Folder 125)
    - 1965 Mar. 18, 58 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 69, Folder 126)
    - 1965 Mar. 18, 62, 57 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 70, Folder 127)
    - 1965 Jul. 22, 64, 50 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 70, Folder 128)
    - 1965 Aug.-Sep, 64, 49 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 70, Folder 129)
      Additional sheets with music schedules, revisions, and notes (holographs in pencil and typescript) laid in
    - 1965 Sep. 20, 64, 45 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 70, Folder 130)
      Typescript (copy) with pencil and ink additions
    - Zulu and the Zayda, 20 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 70, Folder 131)
      Synopsis of Act II
    - Zulu and the Zayda, 51, 61, 37 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 70, Folder 132)
    - Zulu and the Zayda, [31] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 70, Folder 133)
  - Miscellaneous lyrics, 1934-1970; ca. 707 sheets; 27-32 cm. (Box 71, Folder 134-141)
    Holographs in ink and pencil and typescript (in part, copies) with pencil additions (in part, sighed)
    In order as found, loosely organized alphabetically by song title
    Includes lyrics to:
    Alive and Kicking
    Author, Author
    Bless You All
    Call Me Mister
    Destry Rides Again
    Fanny
    Give a Viva
    Green Mansions
    Horshoes and Clover
    Howe and Hummel
    I Can Get It for You Wholesale
    In the Pink
    Let Freedom Sing
    Little Dog Who Laughed
    Lunchtime Follies
    Married Suite
    Michael Todd's Peep Show
    Mr. Brink
    Nantucket
    On Borrowed Time
    Pins and Needles
    Pretty Penny
    Sing Out the News
    Southpaw
    Star and Garter?
    Streets of Paris
    Toujours Forever
    Voskovec and Werich Show
    Wish You Were Here
  - Miscellaneous lyrics and scripts, 1967-1977; ca. 885 sheets; 28-32 cm. (Box 71; 72, Folder 142-143; 144-148)
    Holographs in pencil and ink, and typescript
    Includes drafts of letters, production notes, and miscellaneous notes
    Includes lyrics and scripts to:
    Arouse Arouse!
    Barbara
    Barbra
    Engaged
    Gone With the Wind
    Irving Swifty and Mary Lazar
    Jimmy Carter Campaign Song
    Jonathan Wild
    That's the Ticket
    Waltz of Love
    Wee Bit O'Scotch
    Wonder of the World
    Sketch for proposal for book by Rome entitled "Broadway in Paperback"
    Lyrics for the 1974 Tony Awards show song
  - Miscellaneous lyrics, 1978-1979; ca. 175 sheets; 28-32 cm. (Box 72, Folder 149)
    Holographs in pencil and ink and typescript (in part, copies) with pencil additions
    Includes lyrics for Gone With The Wind, Pins and Needles, and Waltz
  - Miscellaneous lyrics, 1949-1978; 13 notebooks; 29 cm. (Box 73; 74; 75, Folder 150-154; 155-159; 160-164)
    Typescript with pencil additions and holographs in pencil
    Arranged chronologically, all but one contain indices to songs
    Notebooks discarded for preservation purposes
- Production Materials, Contracts, Royalty Statements, and Related Correspondence, 1937-1980; Series III; 1.7' (4 boxes)
  This series is divided into two subseries (A-B). The first consists of production materials including schedules, notes, and lists. These are holographs, manuscripts, and typescripts, which are listed alphabetically by show. Subseries B includes contracts, royalty statements, and related correspondence arranged alphabetically by show, then chronologically, with "Heritage Productions" (recordings) and miscellaneous items at the end. Cross- references have been made from the series introduction for CORRESPONDENCE as well as from individuals in CORRESPONDENCE who also appear in this subseries.
  - Production Materials, III.A
    - Bless You All, 2 items (Box 76, Folder 1)
      Music routine
    - Call Me Mister, 1 item (Box 76, Folder 2)
      List of the company (2 copies, one with addresses added)
    - Gone With the Wind, 1969-1976; 21 items (Box 76, Folder 3)
      Rehearsal and recording schedules, musical cuts, notes, and lists of musical numbers for the Los Angeles, London, and Dallas productions
    - That's the Ticket, 2 items (Box 76, Folder 4)
      Scene 25 Finale (2 copies)
      "Call" sheets
    - Wish You Wer Here, 1952 Jun. 27; 2 items (Box 76, Folder 4)
      Production notes
    - Zulu and the Zayda, 2 items (Box 76, Folder 5)
      Copying Costs of Zulu and the Zayda, and notes (copies, originals laid in with the score)
  - Contracts, Royalty Statements, and Correspondence, III.B
    - Alfred the Average, 1948-1950; 3 items (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Bless You All, 1950-1951; 4 items (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Call Me Mister, 1946-1977; 22 items (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Cinderella, 1953 Mar.-Apr; 4 items (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Destry Rides Again, 1959-1982; 79 items (Box 76, Folder 10-15)
    - Fanny
      - US productions, 1952-1975; 47 items (Box 76, Folder 16-18)
      - Foreign productions, 1955-1971; 56 items (Box 76, Folder 19-23)
      - Motion picture, 1955-1975; 34 items (Box 77, Folder 24-25)
    - Gone With the Wind
      - Japanese production, 1959-1975; 68 items (Box 77, Folder 26-29)
      - British production, 1971-1974; 46 items (Box 77, Folder 30-32)
      - Los Angeles production, 1973 Apr.-Dec; 5 items (Box 77, Folder 33)
      - San Francisco production, 1973 Nov. 26; 3 items (Box 77, Folder 34)
      - Dallas production, 1975-1976; 24 items (Box 77, Folder 35)
      - Miscellaneous productions, 1972-1981; 69 items (Box 77, Folder 36-37)
    - La Grosse Valise, 1967 Jun.-Jul; 3 items (Box 77, Folder 38)
    - Howe And Hummel, 1963-1965; 20 items (Box 78, Folder 39)
    - I Can Get It for You Wholesale, 1961-1965; 77 items (Box 78, Folder 40-42)
    - In the Pink, 1955 Nov. 9; 1 item (Box 78, Folder 43)
    - Jonathan the Wild, 1971-1972; 20 items (Box 78, Folder 44)
    - Little Dog Laughed, 1941 May 21; 1 item (Box 78, Folder 45)
    - Man and Wife, 1962-1963; 3 items (Box 78, Folder 46)
    - Michael Todd's Peep Show, 1950 Apr.-Oct; 4 items (Box 78, Folder 47)
    - Nantucket, 1960 Jul.-Oct; 5 items (Box 78, Folder 48)
    - On Borrowed Time, 1963 Dec; 4 items (Box 78, Folder 49)
    - Paradise Island, 1959 Jun; 2 items (Box 78, Folder 50)
    - Pins and Needles, 1937-1982; 4 items (Box 78, Folder 51-55)
    - Pretty Penny?, ca. 1949; 1 item (Box 78, Folder 56)
    - Saints and Sinners, 1953-1957; 12 items (Box 79, Folder 57)
    - Sing Song Man, 1950-1952; 3 items (Box 79, Folder 58)
    - Sobbin' Women, 1947-1948; 5 items (Box 79, Folder 59)
    - Southpaw, 1966-1969; 9 items (Box 79, Folder 60)
    - That's the Ticket, 1948 Feb; 1 item (Box 79, Folder 61)
    - Toujours Forever, 1964-1968; 11 items (Box 79, Folder 62)
    - Waltz, 1974-1980; 67 items (Box 79, Folder 63-64)
    - Wish You Were Here, 1950-1981; 97 items (Box 79, Folder 65-67)
    - Zulu and the Zayda, 1965-1968; 21 items (Box 79, Folder 68)
    - Heritage Productions (recordings), 1953-1958; 21 items (Box 79, Folder 69)
    - Miscellaneous contracts, royalty statements, and copyright information for songs, shows, recordings, and other works, 1940-1973; 107 items (Box 79, Folder 70-75)
- Correspondence, 1939-1988; Series IV; .8' (2 boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  The correspondence is divided into three subseries: A. Personal; B. Congratulatory Correspondence; and C. Yale Correspondence.
  The personal correspondence is arranged alphabetically by sender then chronologically. Drafts of letters from Rome are filed with the recipient's correspondence and a note has been made. Correspondence concerning the production of shows, contracts, and royalty statements is filed with Series III., PRODUCTION MATERIALS, CONTRACTS, ROYALTY STATEMENTS, AND RELATED CORRESPONDENCE, and cross-references have been made between individuals whose correspondence appears in both places. There are also some drafts of correspondence in Series II. SCRIPTS AND LYRICS, as well as correspondence in Series IX. MISCELLANEOUS ITEMS. A pencil note has been made on the correspondence which was originally found with the disassembled scrapbooks. Cross-references appear within the subseries from names to main entries.
  Subseries B. Congratulatory Correspondence, consists mostly of telegrams, and includes many individuals who are also in subseries A. These are arranged alphabetically by show, then alphabetically by sender, and include many well-known people.
  Subseries C. Yale Correspondence, is arranged chronologically.
  Drafts of letters on legal paper have been copied onto acid-free paper.
  - Personal Correspondence, IV.A
    - Adams, Charles, 1957 Jan. 23-31; 2 items (Box 80, Folder 1)
      Includes typed letter (copy) from Rome
    - American Artist, 1976 Nov. 5; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - American Jewish Congress, 1963 Mar. 25; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - American Jewish Congress. Women's Division, 1979 Apr. 30; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - American Musical and Dramatic Academy, 1 item (Box 80, Folder 1)
      Enclosures
    - American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers, 1943-1985; 6 items (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Arts, Sciences & Professions, Inc., 1951 Oct. 29; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 1)
      Typed letter (copy) from Rome
    - Atchison, Glenn, 1972 Oct. 23; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Auerbach, Arnold M., 1966 Mar. 22; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Barlow, Bob, 1963 Jan. 28; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 2)
      See also: IV. C. Yale Correspondence
    - Baruch, Bernard M., 1964 Dec. 9; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Beck, John, 1978 Feb. 21; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Behrman, Samuel N., 1964 Jan. 7; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 2)
      See also: III. B. PRODUCTION MATERIALS, etc. Fanny - Motion picture, 76/23, p.
    - Bennet, Tony, 1952 Apr. 14; 2 items (Box 80, Folder 2)
      See also: Crusade for Freedom
    - Berlin, Irving, 1962 Oct. 30; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Bob Perilla Associates, 1962 Apr.-Jun; 2 items (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Boston University. University Libraries, 2 items (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Braude, Ben B., 1986 Aug. 23; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Bronx-Lebanon Hospital Center, 1964 Nov. 13; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Burt, John, 1962 Jul. 3; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Central Synagogue, 1965 Feb. 23; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Chagrin, Lionel, 1969 Jan. 17; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Channel 13
      See: WNET/13
    - Chasins, Abram, 1958 Apr. 7-9; 2 items (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Chester, Annette, 1978 Mar. 27; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Chevalier, Maurice, 1960 Jan. 27; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Child Study Association of America, 1942 Oct. 15; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Clemens, Cyril, 1970 Nov. 18; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Collegiate School, 1965 Feb. 14; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Columbia Artists Festivals Corp., 1978 Jul 11; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Crusade for Freedom, 1952 Apr. 16; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 3)
      See also: Bennett, Tony, and Novotná, Jarmila
    - Cushman, Emlyn, 1957-1974; 3 items (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Dalton Schools Inc., 1956 Mar. 19; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - D'Amico, Angela, 1968 Nov. 1; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Daniels, Wilbur, 1988 Feb. 1; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - David, Hal
      See: American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers
    - Dietz, Howard, 1982 Feb. 2; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Dolin, Arnold, 1973 Par. 13; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Drake, Alfred, 1978 May 25; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Dreeszen, Judy, 1962 Jul.-Aug; 2 items (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Duke, Vernon
      See: III. B. PRODUCTION MATERIALS, etc. Call Me Mister, 76/8, p. and Nantucket, 77/36, p.
    - Emanuel Synagogue, 1960 Apr. 25; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Emory University, 1974 Jun. 12; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Engel, Lehman, 1967-1974; 2 items (Box 80, Folder 5)
      See also: III.B. PRODUCTION MATERIALS, etc., Gone With the Wind - Japan, 77/26, p.
    - Fine, Sylvia, 1946 Apr. 19; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Finler, Seymour D., 1968 Jan. 19; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Fitelson, H. William (Bill), 1956-1962; 3 items (Box 80, Folder 5)
      Includes typed letter (copy) from Florence Rome.
      See also: PRODUCTION MATERIALS, etc.
    - Foreign Correspondents' Club of Japan, 1976 Dec. 7-22; 2 items (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Fought, Donald F., 1962 Jul 7; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Francis, Arlene, ca. 1978 Feb. 17; 6 items (Box 80, Folder 5)
      Note from Francis containing fan mail about her radio program with Rome
    - Freeman, Erika and Paul, ca. 1974 May 22; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Freidberg, Sidney, 1961 Jan. 18; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Frewen, Kathryn, 1970 Aug. 25; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Gallagher, P.E., ca. 1955 Feb. 2; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 6)
      Includes copy
    - Gaver, Jessyca Russell, 1966 Dec. 30; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Geismar, Maxwell, 1964 Dec. 5; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Germann, Lilly, 1969 Jan. 19; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Goldman, Harry, 1978 Aug.-Sep; 5 items (Box 80, Folder 6)
      Includes typed letter from Rome, a typed letter signed (copy) from James E. Lyons, and a clipping
    - Goldstein, Eugene, 1985 Dec. 13; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Goodman, Benny, 1955 May 19; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Gottlieb, Polly, 1964 Dec. 9; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Green, Stanley, 1964-1973; 2 items (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Grossman, J., 1970 Dec. 21-31; 2 items (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Hammerstein, Oscar, 1959 Oct. 6; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Harris, Mark
      See: III.B. PRODUCTION MATERIALS, etc. Southpaw, 77/43, p.
    - Hart, Moss, 1959-1960; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Hartley, Neil, 1972 May 22; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Hays, Donald C., 1973 Mar. 20; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Herlie, Eileen, 1970 Mar. 7; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Hillside School (Montclair, New Jersey), 1980 Nov. 5; 2 items (Box 80, Folder 7)
      Program enclosed
    - Horowitz, William, 1966-1973; 3 items (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Hudson, Lewis, 1972 Sep. 26; 2 items (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Ionesco, Eugène, 1961 Apr. 11; 2 items (Box 80, Folder 7)
      Signed pencil sketch enclosed
    - Javits, Jacob K., 1953-1960; 2 items (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Jones, Mr. and Mrs. Guy B., ca. 1939 Jul. 23; 2 items (Box 80, Folder 7)
      Photograph enclosed
    - Jordan, Lee, 1964 Aug. 12; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Kapp, David, 1952-1953; 2 items (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Kaufman, George S.
      See: III.B. PRODUCTION MATERIALS, etc., Pretty Penny, 77/39
    - Kazan, Elia, 1967 May 4; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Kline, John C. (Jack), 1974 Jun. 14; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Klopfer, Mr. and Mrs. Donald S., no date; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Kober, Arthur, 1968-1972; 2 items (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Kroll, Lucy, 1957 Jan. 14-31; 3 items (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Kupferman, Meyer
      See: III.B. PRODUCTION MATERIALS, etc. Gone With the Wind - Japan, 77/26, p.
    - Laba, Benjamin, 1969 Jan. 19; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Lawrence, Justus Baldwin (Jock), 1964-1976; 2 items (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Lazar, Irving Paul, 1958 Feb. 26; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 8)
      See also: III.B. PRODUCTION MATERIALS, etc., Miscellaneous contracts, 78/50, p.
    - Lieberson, Goddard, no year Aug. 28; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Lindsay, Howard, 1964-1967; 3 items (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Logan, Joshua and Nedda, 4 items (Box 80, Folder 8)
      Includes typed letter (copy) from Rome.
      See also: III.B. PRODUCTION MATERIALS, etc., Fanny - Motion picture, 76/23, p.
    - Logan, Thomas, no year May 31; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - MacArthur, Edwin, 1954 Mar. 31; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - McCalls, no date; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 9)
      Typed letter (proposal) from Rome
    - McKenna, Kenneth, 1956 Jan. 27; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - McNab, John, 1987 Jul. 17; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Margolin, Sydney G., M.D., 1964 Nov. 13; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Margolis, Henry M., 1966 Mar. 23; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Marienthal, George E., 1964 Aug. 20; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Mead, Ed Shepherd, 1957 Sep. 29; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Mercer, Johnny, 1957 May 6-9; 3 items (Box 80, Folder 9)
      Includes typed letter (copy) from Rome and ASCAP song list
    - Merrick, David, no date; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 9)
      See also: III.B. PRODUCTION MATERIALS, etc., Fanny, 6/16, Fanny - Foreign productions, 76/19, and I Can Get It for You Wholesale, 77/32, p.
    - Metropolitan Vocational High School, 1956 Mar. 14; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Meyer, Susan
      See: American Artist
    - Miasnick, Michael, no date; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Miss Universe, Inc., 1982 Jan. 5; 2 items (Box 80, Folder 9)
      Includes biographical article
    - National Council of Jewish Women. New York Section, 1969 Feb.-Mar; 2 items (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - New Deal Dinner, no date; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - New York Council of the Arts, Sciences and Professions, 1950 Jun. 8; 2 items (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - New York Heart Association Inc. and Heart Fund, 1968 Apr. 1; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - New York University, 1965 Apr. 12; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Northside Center for Child Development, 1961 May 9; 2 items (Box 80, Folder 10)
      Auction catalogue enclosed
    - Northwood Institute, 1976 Jun. 11; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Novotná, Jarmila, 1952 Apr. 14; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - O'Reilly, J. H., 1973 Oct. 31; 1 item (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Osborn, Paul